question_data = [
    {"question": "Gosho Aoyama created the Detective Conan series.", "answer": "True"},
    {"question": "In Chobits, Hideki found Chii in his apartment.", "answer": "False"},
    {"question": "In Toaru Kagaku no Railgun, espers can reach level 7 or higher.", "answer": "False"},
    {"question": "Clefairy was originally intended to be Ash's starting Pokémon.", "answer": "True"},
    {"question": "The anime Lucky Star is about a girl who is secretly a god.", "answer": "False"},
    {"question": "In The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya, the narrator is nicknamed Kyon.", "answer": "True"},
    {"question": "Studio Ghibli produced Wolf Children and The Boy and the Beast.", "answer": "False"},
    {"question": "Ash's Pikachu refuses to enter a Pokéball.", "answer": "True"},
    {"question": "In To Love-Ru, Golden Darkness is sent to kill Lala Deviluke.", "answer": "False"},
    {"question": "In the 1988 film Akira, Tetsuo destroys Tokyo.", "answer": "True"}
]
